(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-09T22:44:07.653948",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
3D新衣装お披露目！ 重大告知
[New 3D Outfit Reveal! Big Announcement!]
Daisuke
作詞：Y&Co. 作曲：田村哲也
[Daisuke
Lyrics: Y&Co. Music: Tetsuya Tamura]
I'm a country girl.
but you're a super city boy
I'm a natural girl,
but you're a prince for me
Everyday wondering how I become your girl.
Everynight I'm feeling your body in my dreams.
I can't sleep at all
hello morning sun
My love, my crush,
I wanna tell you my feeling
Please tell me now,
how do you feel me?
みんなー！
Everyone!
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you 're one for you
Everytime,
everywhere.
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
I'm a natural girl,
but you're prince for me
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy
Everyday wondering how I become your girl
Every night I'm feeling your body in my dreams
I can't sleep at all, hello morning sun
My love, my crush, I wanna tell you my feeling
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you 're one for you
Everytime,
everywhere.
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you 're one for you
Everytime,
everywhere.
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
Let's go!
I lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I ignored before
You left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much, but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets
Make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not
keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all ok
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart
Give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
One, two, three, let's go!
Took a bet on love, it's better than I coulda dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh, what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
'Til the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up
and don't look back again
Carbonated Love!
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on going until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up and begin
Carbonated Love!
HiRyS! It's IRyS from hololive English -Promise-! Woohoo!
Look at who we have here, aren't they so cute? 可愛いすね、こいつら！
Look at who we have here, aren't they so cute? Aren't these guys cute?!
いや、頑張ってね。一緒に踊っていただいたんで。いや、嬉しい！
Thanks for trying your best! I'm so glad they danced along with me!
And, uh, before we, you know, get into all sorts of things... First off, please use the hashtag #IRySBDay2026... Oh, this way!
#IRySBDay2026! こちらのハッシュタグぜひ、ぜひツイートしてくださいね、感想など！
#IRySBDay2026! Please tweet using this hashtag with your thoughts and feedback!
If you have anything you want to talk about this live, please use the hashtag. These RyS'ers will definitely get on their phones later on too to tweet with the hashtag.
And... have you guys noticed something different? なんか、なんかアイリス、いつもと見た目違うっしょ？
And... have you guys noticed something different? Don't I look a bit different than usual?
どう？レースクイーン！
What do you think? A race queen!
あ、興奮してる。They look very excited! Yeah, they are going... they are going mad, yes!
Oh, they're excited! They look very excited! Yeah, they are going... they are going mad, yes!
それぐらい素晴らしいっしょ？Finally, the race queen outfit is real! Yay!
Isn't it just that amazing? Finally, the race queen outfit is real! Yay!
いや、いいね。ありがとうございます。サクラじゃないよ！
Yeah, it's great. Thank you so much. They're not paid actors!
はい。Alrighty then, uh, first off though, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods! Yes, here is the lineup this time!
Yes. Alrighty then, uh, first off though, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods! Yes, here is the lineup this time!
Yes, we're introducing merch pretty early on this time. It's supposed to pop out... この辺かな？あ、はい！グッズは今回こちらになります！
Yes, we're introducing merch pretty early on this time. It's supposed to pop out... Around here? Oh, yes! Here is the merchandise this time!
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026! アイリス生誕、えっと、誕生日記念2026！
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026! IRyS Birthday... uh, Birthday Celebration 2026!
All right, let me introduce the goods one by one. First off, there is this one.
はい！ガイリスも喜んでるね。Yes, first up, we have the Acrylic Diorama Stand!
Yes! The GuyRyS are happy too. Yes, first up, we have the Acrylic Diorama Stand!
...のジオラマスタンドRyS！
...diorama StandRyS!
イラストは、あの、ピスケ先生！
The illustration is by... Piske-sensei!
今回の衣装もピスケ先生なんですよ。うふふ。
This outfit is also designed by Piske-sensei! Hehehe.
This diorama stand features IRyS in her race queen outfit perfectly,
capturing the atmosphere of this 3D live stage, yes!
みんなも買おうね！イェーイ！はい。
You should all buy it too! Yay! Okay.
And then, the second one is this one. Yes!
The ChibiRyS Tote Bag!
It's so cute!
Illustration, as in the... on the tote bag, is by Lien-sensei!
The illustration on the tote bag is by Lien-sensei!
いつもLien先生ありがとう！ Thank you so much, Lien, all the time!
Thank you as always, Lien-sensei! Thank you so much, Lien, all the time!
It's so cute. I love ChibiRyS.
This tote features mini IRyS in her...
casual outfit, yes, drawn by Lien-sensei. So cute!
Lien先生に描いてもらった、カジュアルIRySのちびになってます。可愛いトート。
It features a chibi version of casual IRyS drawn by Lien-sensei. Such a cute tote!
ぜひ普段使いしてください。お出かけで使ってね。
Please use it for everyday outings! Go out with it!
Please use it when you go shopping and what not.
And with the simple design, it's perfect for everyday use.
You can pair it with other merch that'll be introduced right after this.
So show off your IRyS pride! Yay!
この後に紹介するグッズとも合わせて使えるんで、楽しみにしててね。はい。
You can use it together with the merch I'll show next, so look forward to it! Yes!
And then, the third one...
is the Race Queen RyS Keychain!
こちらの素晴らしい衣装のキーチェーンになってます。
This beautiful outfit is now a keychain!
可愛いあろう？
Isn't it cute?
あ、欲しいの？ Oh, they wanted it already! They wanted it already!
Oh, you want it? Oh, they wanted it already! They wanted it already!
まだダメ！ここからだよ。
Not yet! It starts from here.
注文するよね？ You guys are going to buy it, right?
You're going to order it, right? You guys are going to buy it, right?
Yeah! 1セットで終わらないよね？
Yeah! You won't stop at just one set, right?
もう、爆買いしてくれるそうです。はい。
Apparently, they're going to go on a shopping spree. Yes!
This is the new plushie featuring my new outfit!
新衣装のIRySがぬいぐるみのキーホルダーになっちゃったよ。
IRyS in her new outfit has become a plushie keychain!
It's definitely cute on its own, but you can also carry it with its face peeking from the outer pocket of the tote bag!
ぜひトートバッグの中にポンって入れちゃって、一緒にお出かけしてね。
So pop it right into your tote bag, and go out together!
And then, the last one is the YabaiRyS Pouch!
みんなの大好きなヤバイリスだよ！
It's everyone's favorite YabaiRyS!
何を考えてるんでしょう？ I wonder what she's thinking with that face of hers, yes.
I wonder what she is thinking... I wonder what she's thinking with that face of hers, yes.
Yes, YabaiRyS is back again! This face pouch with its high-impact design—yes, it's high impact—
can also be attached to a bag handle.
先ほど紹介したトートバッグの取ってにポンってつけると、とっても可愛いよ。
It looks super cute when you clip it onto the handle of the tote bag I just introduced.
Yes, you can use it with the tote bag. Just put it on the tote bag, and it'll be a perfect set!
トートとぬい、and the pouch, as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world, yes!
With the tote, plushie, and the pouch as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world, yes!
あ、ちなみに、 this is pouch, by the way. Just clarifying.
Ah, by the way, this is a pouch, by the way. Just clarifying.
これはポーチになってます。 So you can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things. Yay!
This is a pouch, so you can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things. Yay!
Okay, and then, here are the full set bonuses! Yes, the postcard!
Illustration is the same illustration from Piske-sensei for the acrylic stand.
The illustration is the same illustration by Piske-sensei used for the acrylic stand.
ピスケ先生の素晴らしいイラストをこちらのポストカードでも使ってます。
This wonderful illustration by Piske-sensei is also used for this postcard!
The limited edition features a handwritten message, yes!
数量限定版は、直筆メッセージ ＆ 箔押し複製サイン入り...
The limited edition features a handwritten message and a foil-stamped duplicate signature...
ポストカードです！
postcard!
なのでメッセージは直筆、直筆はメッセージの方です。はい。
So the message is handwritten, the handwritten part is the message. Yes.
数量限定、買うよね？
You're going to buy the limited edition, right?
Yeah! I want you guys to be as hyped as them, yeah!
The standard version comes with a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message as well!
通常版ももちろんあるんで、箔押し複製サイン ＆ メッセージ入りポストカードになってます。
Of course, the standard version is also available as a postcard with a foil-stamped duplicate signature and message.
So you can get both! 限定版も通常版もぜひゲットしてね。
So you can get both! Please make sure to get both the limited and standard editions!
イェーイ！
Yay!
みんな可愛いな。 You guys are so cute.
Everyone is so cute. You guys are so cute.
Look at how big their heads are. 頭デカいね。
Look at how big their heads are. Your heads are so big...
あ、刺される！あ、痛いよ、痛い、痛いよ。
Ah, I'm getting poked! Ah, it hurts, hurts, it hurts!
君たちはしょうがないな。
You guys are hopeless.
There are plenty more announcements coming up, yeah! If you guys can tell, I'm already introducing merch,
so there's a lot of other things coming up.
この後もね、色んな大きな告知があるんで、
There are lots of other big announcements coming up after this,
ぜひ最後まで見ててくださいね。楽しみに聞いててね。
so please watch until the very end! Look forward to it!
There are still big announcements after this, so stay tuned!
じゃ、続きやるぞー！ Let's go on with the live! Woo!
Now, let's keep going! Let's go on with the live! Woo!
はっ
Ha!
JANE DOE
[Title: JANE DOE]
うー
Ooh...
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world...
二人だけみたいだね
...it's just the two of us, isn't it?
なんて
I just...
少しだけ
...had a little...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...dream like that.
つま先に月明かり
Moonlight on my toes,
花束の香り
the scent of a bouquet,
指に触れる指
a finger touching my finger.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I have to go now,
何もかも忘れて
forgetting everything.
ガラスの上を
Walking barefoot...
裸足のまま歩く
...across the glass.
痛むごとに
With every stab of pain...
血が流れて落ちていく
...blood flows and falls.
お願い
Please...
その赤い足跡を
...follow those red footprints...
辿って
...and...
会いに来て
come see me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusty pool.
靴箱の中 隠した林檎
An apple hidden inside the shoe locker.
萎びた君の肌に
Scars left...
残る傷跡
...on your withered skin.
犬のように泳いだ迷子
A lost child who swam like a dog.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ここにいるよ
I'm here.
何をしてるの
What are you doing?
ずっと見てるよ
I've been watching.
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
そばにいてよ
Stay by my side,
遊びに行こうよ
let's go play.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を
Walking barefoot...
裸足のまま歩く
...across the glass.
痛むごとに
With every stab of pain...
血が流れて落ちていく
...blood flows and falls.
お願い
Please...
その赤い足跡を
...follow those red footprints...
辿って
...and...
会いに来て
come see me.
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world...
二人だけみたいだね
...it's just the two of us, isn't it?
なんて
I just...
少しだけ
...had a little...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...dream like that.
Gaze on Me!
[Title: Gaze on Me!]
揺らせ一秒 駆けたなら summer girls
Shake it — one second, sprint and we're summer girls!
夢への道はストレート
The path to our dreams is straight ahead.
視線誰にも譲れない
My eyes won't give way to anyone.
Please, gaze on me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
Surely, a fantastic time's about to start!
(La la la la la la... ゴールは Spot light)
(La la la la la la... the finish is the spotlight)
(La la la la la la... I'm the heroine)
(La la la la la la... キミを頂戴)
(La la la la la la... I want you tonight)
(Please, gaze on me!)
(きっと始まる Fantastic time)
(Surely, a fantastic time's about to start!)
みんな準備はいいですか？ Burning
Everyone — you ready? Burning!
うなずいて陽炎も Heat up
Nod along — even the heat shimmer's turning hot!
どうしよう上昇アガる空気
Oh my — the vibe's rising, we're getting hyped!
Let's go! さあ 太陽 燃えて 最高
Let's go! Now, the sun is blazing and it's the best!
Mate 負けられない 興奮もハートも
Mate, I can't lose, my excitement and my heart...
駆け引きは no no
...there are no tactics, no, no!
Gate 開いたなら 一瞬のドラマ
Gate, if it's opened, it's a momentary drama!
走れ 夏の方へ
Run towards the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆け出したら Summer girls
Shake for a second, once we start running, summer girls!
夢への道は ストレート
The path to our dreams is straight.
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
It's bound to be an exciting, fantastic time!
La la la... ゴールは Spotlight
La la la... The goal is the spotlight.
La la la... I'm the heroine
La la la... キミを頂戴
La la la... Give me your heart.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
It's bound to be an exciting, fantastic time!
絶対 最上 掴みたい Feeling
I definitely want to seize that ultimate feeling.
全身全霊 めぐるから Get heart
With my whole body and soul, I'll win your heart!
テンション高揚 欲しいモノへ
My tension is rising, towards what I want.
今 Ride on time って It's show time
Now, it's ride on time, meaning it's show time!
Peak 迎える時 遠慮はいらない
When reaching the peak, no holding back!
せめぎあい Oh oh
Clashing with each other, oh oh!
Spark 汗とプライド ズレた運命
Spark! Sweat and pride, a crossed fate.
連れて夏の方へ
Take me towards the summer!
挑む世界は 魅惑の Sunlight floor
The world we challenge is the alluring sunlight floor.
天井知らずの ボルテージ
A limitless voltage!
火照る季節を モノにして
Make the hot season yours!
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい Exciting time
I want to make you dizzy in this exciting time!
La la la... ゴールは Spotlight
La la la... The goal is the spotlight.
La la la... I'm the heroine
La la la... キミを頂戴
La la la... Give me your heart.
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい Exciting time
I want to make you dizzy in this exciting time!
関係ない どんな私だって
It doesn't matter what kind of person I am.
真夏 駆け出せたら Venus
If I can run into midsummer, I'll be Venus!
アツくなれば一歩で Change and happy
If it gets hot, in one step, change and happy!
眩しすぎる今日を 踊るように手に入れよう
Let's capture this too-bright day like we're dancing!
さあ Here we go!
Now, here we go!
ビートは止まらない
The beat won't stop!
Keep 思うままに 身を預けて
Keep surrendering your body as you wish.
灼熱へ Go go
Into the scorching heat, go go!
Warp 本能のリズム 打ち鳴らして
Warp, play the rhythm of instinct!
走れ夏の方へ
Run towards the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆け出したら Summer girls
Shake for a second, once we start running, summer girls!
夢への道は ストレート
The road to our dreams is straight.
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
It's bound to start, a fantastic time!
La la la... ゴールは Spotlight
La la la... The goal is the spotlight.
La la la... I'm the heroine
La la la... キミを頂戴
La la la... Give me your heart.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
It's bound to start, a fantastic time!
愛♡スクリーム！
Love Scream!
教えて！もっと あなたの事
Tell me more, more about you!
Tell me more, more, more
聞かせて！もっと あなたの声
Let me hear more, more of your voice!
Let me hear more, more, more
こんなドキドキ もう抑え切れない
This heart fluttering, I can't suppress it anymore!
All I need you, oh All I need you
All I need is you, oh All I need is you.
友達は卒業 運命の私
Graduating from being friends, the me of destiny...
見つけて欲しいの
...I want you to find me!
One! 勇気を出して
One! Gather your courage!
Two! 見つめる作戦
Two! The staring strategy!
Three! 瞳と目が合えば
Three! If our eyes meet...
Four! 止められない Yeah yeah yeah
Four! I can't stop it, yeah yeah yeah!
この恋 この愛で Melt melt とろけちゃうよ
With this love, this affection, I'm melting away!
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling!
届け！大好き！
Reach you! I love you!
愛、愛、スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, let's scream it out!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！ Okay!
Scream! Ice cream! Okay!
愛、愛、スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, love, scream, let's scream it out!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント！
Chocomint!
よりも、あなた♡
More than that, you! <3
IRySちゃん！
IRyS-chan!
はーい！
Hi!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりもあ・な・た
More than strawberry flavor, I like you!
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
はーい！
Hi!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりもあ・な・たー
More than cookies and cream, I like you!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Hi!
何が好き？
What do you like?
モチロン大好き AiScream
Of course, we love AiScream!
止められない
I can't stop this!
Yeah Yeah Yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah, with this love and affection
Melt Melty 溶けちゃうよ Mom
Melt Melty, I'm melting away!
ねぇ？
Hey?
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
届け！大好き！
Let it reach you! I love you!
アイ愛スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai-AiScream, Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイアイスクリーム OK!
Scream, Ai-AiScream! (OK!)
アイ愛スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai-AiScream, Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム！
Scream, Ice cream!
おねがい見つけて “my darling”
Please find me, "my darling"
おねがい気づいて “my darling”
Please notice me, "my darling"
One 勇気を出して
One, muster up your courage
Two 近づく作戦
Two, the plan to get closer
Three 手と手が触れて
Three, our hands touch
Fall
止められない
I can't stop this!
Yeah Yeah Yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah, with this love and affection
Melt Melty 溶けちゃうよ Mom
Melt Melty, I'm melting away!
ねぇ？
Hey?
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling
それは！ アナタ！
And that is... you!
アイ愛スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai-AiScream, Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイアイスクリーム OK!
Scream, Ai-AiScream! (OK!)
アイ愛スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai-AiScream, Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム！
Scream, Ice cream!
アイ愛スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai-AiScream, Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイアイスクリーム OK!
Scream, Ai-AiScream! (OK!)
アイ愛スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai-AiScream, Scream, let's shout it out!
スクリーム アイスクリーム！
Scream, Ice cream!
La la la la la la love love
La la la la la la love love...
モニタリング (Best Friend Remix)
Lyrics, Music: DECO*27
[Title: Monitoring (Best Friend Remix)]
[Lyrics, Music: DECO*27]
ねえあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
知ってるよ ピクンピクン震えてさ 声もダダ漏れなんだわ
I know. You're shaking and trembling, and your voice is leaking out.
正直に言っちゃえば バレてんだし言っちゃえば
To be honest, it's totally obvious, so just say it.
聞いてんの？ 普通普通平気だよ みんな分かってないだけ うつうつ
Are you listening? It's totally fine, everyone just doesn't get it. Feeling down?
もしもーし
Hello?
ねえ大丈夫？
Hey, are you okay?
んー、心配だから今からそっち行くね
Hmm, I'm worried, so I'll head over to your place now.
ねえあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
知ってるよ グスングスン凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラでいいんじゃない？
I know. You're sobbing and feeling down, why not just vent at solo karaoke?
朝が来るまで一緒トーク もっと泣いたって 何度だって受け止めてあげる
We can talk until morning. Even if you cry more,
I'll catch you every single time.
もう我慢しないでいっぱいはいてね
So don't hold back anymore, just let it all out.
うーわっ！ お願いきみが欲しいの 慰めさせてベストフレンド
Ooh, wow! Please, I want you. Let me comfort you, best friend.
愛の才能で 泣いてくれるかい？ きみのツラい 抱きしめたい ねぇいいでしょう？
With my talent for love, will you cry for me?
I want to embrace your pain, hey, is that okay?
分け合って乗り越えたいんだってば
I'm telling you, I want us to share it and get through it together.
うーわっ！ お願いきみが欲しいの 笑い飛ばしてポップステップジャンプ
Ooh, wow! Please, I want you. Let's laugh it off and pop-step-jump!
さあ行こうぜ
Come on, let's go!
分けてくれるかい？ きみの重い 暗い想い ねぇいいでしょう？
Will you share it with me? Your heavy, dark feelings,
hey, is that okay?
寄り添って救いたいんだってば
I'm telling you, I want to be by your side and save you.
見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, want to see, want to see...
...きみの中
...inside you.
見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, want to see, want to see...
ねえあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり悔しがってんの
Hey, I know. I know you're feeling frustrated all alone.
知ってるよ グスングスン終わるまで きみを決して諦めない
I know. Until the sobbing ends, I will never give up on you.
ねえあたし知ってるよ きみはできる子知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're capable.
つらい時は弱いくらいで丁度いい あたしきみの味方だよ
When things are tough, showing weakness is just right.
I am on your side.
うーわっ！ お願いきみが欲しいの 名前を呼んでよ いつだって会いに参上
Ooh, wow! Please, I want you. Call my name, I'll come see you anytime.
きみはひとりかい？ それは違う ひとりじゃない ねぇいいでしょう？
Are you all alone? That's not right, you're not alone,
hey, is that okay?
ソロプレイはお仕舞いなんだってば
I'm telling you, solo play is over.
きみがどんなときも あたし側にいるわ
No matter when, I will be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ
I will always be watching over you.
そうよ 怖くないのよ
That's right, there is nothing to fear.
うーわっ！ お願いきみが欲しいの 慰めさせて
Ooh, wow! Please, I want you. Let me comfort you...
...ベストフレンド 愛の才能で
...best friend, with the talent of love,
泣いてくれるかい
Will you cry for me?
きみのツライ 抱き締めたい
I want to embrace your pain.
ねえいいでしょう？
Hey, is that okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいん
I want us to share it and get through it...
だっだっだってば
...because I really do!
お願いきみが欲しいの
Please, I want you.
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off and...
ホップステップジャンプでいこうぜ
...let's go with a hop, step, and jump!
分けてくれるかい
Will you share it with me?
きみの重い 暗い思い
Your heavy, dark thoughts...
覗きたい
...I want to look inside them.
吸い取って 救いたいん
I want to absorb them and save you...
だっだっだってば
...because I really do!
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know.
きみがひとり 涙してるの 知ってるの
I know that you're crying all alone.
グスングスン凹んでさ
Sniffling and feeling down...
弱音ヒトカラいいんじゃない？
...isn't it fine to sing solo and let it out?
ずっと一緒 もっと泣いたって
We're always together, even if you cry more.
何度だって 受け止めてあげる
I will support you as many times as it takes.
もう我慢しないで
Don't hold back anymore,
出してってってってってば
just let it all out!
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Beat, beat, baby
Music gets you crazy
Shock me tonight
Go beat crazy!
Fun, fun, baby
Dancin' feelin' hazy
Dancing, feeling hazy
Shake out of sight
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
No lovey-dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
Keep on moving your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go!
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go!
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
Go beat crazy!
Boom, boom, baby
Come and shake your booty
Dig it tonight
Go beat crazy!
Go, go, baby
Show me that you're ready
Get satisfied
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
No lovey-dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
Keep on moving your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go!
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go!
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
Go beat crazy!
Beat, beat, baby
Fun, fun, baby
Go beat crazy!
Boom, boom, baby
Go, go, baby
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go!
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
Go beat crazy!
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Are you ready?
カリスマックス
Charismax!
Everybody make some noise!
誰も真似できやしないな
No one can ever imitate us
StarのGuidance
Star's guidance
バズりまくり
Going viral nonstop
常にTacticalに
Always being tactical
Haterたちにご提案
A suggestion for the haters
ディスるより Do what you love
Instead of dissing, do what you love
朝から晩まで Ring a Ring a Ling
From morning till night, Ring a Ring a Ling
勝ちや負け気にするのは論外
Caring about winning or losing is out of the question
「ミスるの問題」
"The problem of making mistakes"
とか言ってんのが大問題
Saying things like that is the big problem
Alright 自分自身が正解
Alright! I'm the correct answer
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone must always uphold their conviction
We are! We are! No. 1
カリスマックス
Charismax!
最強のマインド
The strongest mind
カリスマックス
Charismax!
時代塗り替える
Rewriting the era
カリスマックス
Charismax!
世界が驚く
The world is amazed
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy man
All of them, crazy crazy man
Crazy crazy man
常識壊してゆく カリスマックス
Breaking common sense: Charismax!
まるで人生はStageみたいだ
Life is just like a stage
皆が役者
Everyone's an actor
何でもできる そう君は何でもできる
You can do anything, yes, you can do anything
Wannabeたちにご提案
A suggestion for the wannabes
今すぐに Do what you want
Right now, do what you want
世界に響かす Ding a Ding a Ling
Resonate worldwide, Ding a Ding a Ling
空気は読むより変えてくStyle
Instead of reading the atmosphere, we change it—our style
はみ出す天才
A genius who stands out
てか愛想笑いなんてしない
I don't fake a smile
Alright 答えは明快
Alright! The answer is clear
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone must always uphold their conviction
We are! We are! No. 1
カリスマックス
Charismax!
才能解き放つ
Unleashing talent
カリスマックス
Charismax!
進化をし続ける
Continuously evolving
カリスマックス
Charismax!
限界超えてゆく
Going beyond limits
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy woman
All of them, crazy crazy woman
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone must always uphold their conviction
We are! We are!
No. 1
カリスマックス
Charismax!
最強のマインド
The strongest mind
カリスマックス
Charismax!
時代塗り替える
Rewriting the era
カリスマックス
Charismax!
世界が驚く
The world is amazed
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy man
All of them, crazy crazy man
カリスマックス
Charismax!
才能解き放つ
Unleashing talent
カリスマックス
Charismax!
進化をし続ける
Continuously evolving
カリスマックス
Charismax!
限界超えてゆく
Going beyond limits
どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy woman
All of them, crazy crazy woman
Crazy crazy man
常識壊してゆく カリスマックス
Breaking common sense: Charismax!
Yeah!
Aha!
Can I get it, get it, get it, get all your attention?
Can I get all your attention?
I bet you don't know me yet
君の奥底まで
To the very depths of you,
穿つ目線で
with my piercing gaze,
溢れる様 IQ ammo
overflowing like IQ ammo,
獲る天下
I'll conquer the world.
A catalyst, I know. When I say go, put your hands up
混沌の最中に
In the midst of chaos,
降臨した女神
the goddess descended.
I freeze it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know but you don't
震憾させる異脳
My extraordinary mind will shake you.
I'mma go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine
Can't stop 煌めく my fantasy
Can't stop my sparkling fantasy,
Now you see
星空を呑む
Swallowing the starry sky,
染まるんだ私色に
it gets dyed in my color.
Hidden deep within my universe
Come find me now
Hear the voice that's calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を見せてあげるから
Since I will show you the essence of this unseen world...
Baby, for now
Calm down, lemme focus
Under my spell like hypnosis
So don't get too close when I'm
(Come-a, come-a, comin through)
You wanna roll with me?
We take 'em down, yes
I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do
脳髄まで bulletproof
bulletproof to the core.
Cold when I do what I do, when I focus
On me
Back at my best, I finesse
私の脳裏に潜む
Lurking in the back of my mind,
怪物のは no secret
the monster within is no secret.
冷静に cool, my attitude
Cool and calm, my attitude.
Uh-uh, target in my sight, locked in, ready to shoot, like
Mayday, this is an emergency
Working under pressure, baby, I can do this in my sleep
世の理だって
Even the laws of this world,
書き換えてしまう様な頭脳
I have a brain that can rewrite them.
When I go, when I go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine
Won't stop 煌めく my fantasy
Won't stop my sparkling fantasy,
Now you see
銀河を覆う
Covering the galaxy,
音色をそう、轟かす様に
I'll make its tone resound.
Hidden deep within my universe
Come find me now
Clear my mind of all these doubts
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄
The essence of this unseen world...
この目で見たいから
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Baby, for now
Calm down, lemme focus
Under my spell like hypnosis
So don't get too close when I'm
(Come-a, come-a, comin through)
You wanna roll with me?
We take 'em down, yes
I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do
脳髄まで bulletproof
bulletproof to the core.
Cold when I do what I do, when I focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh
垂れろ頭 Don't break my focus
Bow your heads, don't break my focus.
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
I'mma get you talkin bout it loud, can't get rid of me now
I'mma get you talking about it loud, can't get rid of me now.
唯一無二 so I'm crowned, put my feet on the ground
One and only, so I'm crowned, put my feet on the ground.
まあ掻っ攫ってくわエース, piece of cake, it's no stress
Well, I'll sweep them away as the ace, piece of cake, it's no stress.
銀河中を魅了してく, what's next? Take a guess
Charming the entire galaxy, what's next? Take a guess.
Yes, I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, 脳髄まで bulletproof
I tell you what to do, bulletproof to the core.
Cold when I do what I do, when I focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh
垂れろ頭 Don't break my focus
Bow your heads, don't break my focus.
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind (Focus)
DARK ARIA
The time has come
to pack away
all the joys
You don't wanna hear
my apology
Get it off my chest
I would do my best
I know what you fear
similarities
we possess
Never will I pass the test
The scene is fading
Can my soul be put to rest?
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like
fairytales?
Far from this tragedy
Sad you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels wings lifting and setting me free
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like
fairytales?
Far from this tragedy
Sad you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels wings lifting and setting me free
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
Woo!
Oh, we're getting towards the end of the live.
There were so many beautiful songs and so many beautiful guests!
I love the glasses,
the Karin-max and Daisuki glasses. It's good stuff!
And we're getting to the end,
which means announcements! Yeah!
But first off, before this live, I mean, after this live...
...there will be a members-only part as well, so join the RyS-family today!
えっと、この後もね、あの、メン限パートもあるので、
Also, after this, there's going to be a members-only part as well,
ぜひ、メンバーに、メンバーシップに入って来い！
so please join the member... membership!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
歌、歌うんでね。Yes.
I'll be singing, so yes.
Are you guys ready for the announcement?
すっごくすっごく嬉しい告知があります！
I have a really, really exciting announcement!
There's a big, big announcement I'm really, really happy about!
I can't wait! I'm super happy I get to share it with you guys!
はい、嬉しい告知、行きます！
Alright, here comes the exciting announcement!
まずは、こちらをご覧ください！
First, please take a look at this!
Please watch this short video!
願いを叶える魔法があるとするなら
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes
それは、あなた。
It would be you
2026年 10月6日
[2026 Oct 6th]
日本 東京
[JAPAN, TOKYO]
IRyS 1st Concert
会場 SGC HALL ARIAKE
[VENUE: SGC HALL ARIAKE]
そしてわたしは、あなたに贈る
And I will gift you...
奇跡で出来た、この希望を。
...with hope made of miracles.
ということで！
And so!
Yes, IRyS, I will be having my very first solo live! Yay!
In Tokyo, Japan!
アイリス、なんと、初めてのソロライブ、
I, IRyS, will be having my very first solo live,
日本で開催されることが決定しました！ウフーー！
and it has been confirmed to be held in Japan! Woohoo!
Yes, it will be in Tokyo at the SGC Hall Ariake!
えっと、場所は東京のSGCホール有明でございます！
The venue is the SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo!
日程は、10月6日！
The date is October 6th!
It's going to be on a Tuesday...
はい、火曜日でございますね。
...yes, it's on a Tuesday.
It will be happening on October 6th, Tuesday, yeah!
Mark your calendars!
カレンダーに書いておくれや。
Make sure to write it in your calendars!
ずっとね、本当に夢に見ていたステージに
I'm so incredibly happy to stand
立てることをすごく嬉しく思いますし、
on a stage that I've always dreamed of,
本当にみんなの応援のおかげです。ありがとうございます。
and it's truly thanks to all your support. Thank you so much.
It's all thanks to your guys' support that I get to have this opportunity,
so thank you so much for all your support!
アイリス、がんばるぞ！イェーイ！
IRyS is going to do her best! Yay!
えっとね、
Well,
I'm working really hard to make this live
an amazing one for you guys, a very magical one!
So, please look forward to it, make sure you definitely come!
If you don't come, I'll be sad. If you don't come, you'll also regret it, yes!
あの、ライブに向けて準備めちゃくちゃがんばってるんで、
I'm working really hard preparing for this live,
素晴らしいライブになるようにがんばってるんで、
and doing my best to make it an amazing show,
ぜひ会場へ観に来てくださーい！
so please come see it at the venue!
観に行かないとアイリス悲しいし、みんなも後悔するぞ。
If you don't come, I'll be sad, and you'll regret it too!
はい！
Alright!
そして、and along with it, yes!
And along with it, yes!
I will also be releasing my very first full album! Woohoo!
なんと、アイリス、初のフルアルバム出ます！
Unbelievably, I'll be releasing my first full album!
なんだかんだ言って、今までEPだったんですけど、フルアルバムは初めてです。
We've had EPs so far, but this is my first full album.
Yeah, I've released EPs in the past, but this is the very first full album!
So look forward to it, there's a lot of songs!
The album jacket...
Yeah!
Album jacket is by Kito Kouta-sensei. It's very cute!
The album title is called DANGERyS, yes.
何でも'RyS'を付ければいいってもんじゃないかもしれないけど、
It might not be the best to just attach 'RyS' to everything,
ちょうどはまったんでね、'DANGERyS'な
but it fit perfectly, so it's a DANGERyS,
とても危険的でホットなアルバムになってます。Yes.
very dangerous and hot album. Yes.
えっと、there are many songs written by...
Well, there are many songs written by...
...all sorts of songwriters from all over the world.
And there's going to be a lot of Eurobeat songs, but also songs that are not Eurobeat as well. New genres as well.
So I hope you guys look forward to that.
ね、あの、国内外の様々なクリエイターにユーロビート以外の楽曲も
Right? We've had various creators from both Japan and overseas make non-Eurobeat tracks as well,
多数作ってもらってます。A lot of new songs.
plenty of them. A lot of new songs.
And I will be performing, of course, performing one of the songs for you today!
今日もね、あの、1曲披露しようかなと思ってます。Song showcase, yay!
I'm planning to perform one song today too. Song showcase, yay!
The song I'll be showcasing for you today was written and arranged by...
the Eurobeat circle SOUND HOLIC! Yes!
Yes, they are very famous for Eurobeat. So I'm really glad, I'm really happy to be able to work with them. Thank you so much!
えっとね、今回、あの、披露する楽曲は、作曲、編曲、国内のユーロビートを得意とするクリエイターさん
So, the song I'll be performing today has been composed and arranged by a domestic creator specializing in Eurobeat...
SOUND HOLICさんでございます！ありがとうございます！
specifically, SOUND HOLIC! Thank you so much!
新たなユーロビートの見せ方になると思うんで、楽しみにしてて。
I think it will show a new side of Eurobeat, so look forward to it.
It's Eurobeat, but there's something about it that's also not very Eurobeat. So I hope you guys know what I mean when I sing it.
The digital release will be happening on... 12:00 AM JST, the upcoming 12:00 AM JST after this. So, make sure you stream it on Spotify...
and other streaming services. Yay!
このあとね、えっと、デジタルリリースも各配信サイトで行われます。
After this, the digital release will go live on various streaming sites.
えっと、0時に配信されます。楽しみにしててね！
Um, it will be released at midnight. Look forward to it!
すごくド派手な曲です。楽しみだ。
It's a super flashy song. I'm excited!
And as for the details of the album, I will be talking about that...
at the very end of this live. So be sure to stick till the end!
アルバムの詳細は、このあと最後の方にね、えっと、いろいろ説明しちゃうんで、最後まで見てね！
As for the album's details, I'll explain everything at the very end, so please watch until the end!
Alright then, please listen to my new song, BE MY FLAME!
新しい曲聞いてください、BE MY FLAME。
Please listen to my new song, BE MY FLAME.
Blazin' fire
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
Tension rising to the top, won't look back, I'll never stop
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot, it's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on, I wanna confess, baby, oh baby, I'm gettin' obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be, wanna be ready for more
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm only getting started
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream,
Wild desire fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
So, how did you guys like my birthday 3D live?
We had so much going on from the new 3D outfit reveal,
new merch, to my first album announcement,
solo live announcement, and new song performances!
I think it was packed with so much, so I'd like to give you guys a recap and share the details.
ライブ本編はどうでしたか？
How did you like the live stream?
色々とね、告知盛りだくさんだったと思うので、改めておさらいと詳細をお伝えします。
Since there was a lot of news announced, let me go over the details with you all again.
まずはグッズから！ First up, the merch.
First up, the merchandise!
We have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS, illustrated by Ninunonipisuke-sensei.
The ChibiRyS Tote Bag, illustrated by Lian-sensei.
The Race QueenRyS Keychain, which is a really cute race queen plushie keychain,
And the YabaiRyS Pouch.
For full set bonuses, the limited edition includes a postcard with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped autograph.
The standard version includes a postcard with both a foil-stamped message and autograph.
The sales will start at 1:15 PM, which is like real soon, if not maybe even now!
フルセットを買っていただいた方には、数量限定版は直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
For those who purchase the full set, the limited-edition version comes with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped copy of the autograph on a postcard.
通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りポストカードになります。
The standard version comes with a postcard featuring a foil-stamped copy of my autograph and message.
このあと1時15分にカートオープンするよ！もうすぐだよ！
The cart will open in just a bit at 1:15 PM! It's almost time!
続いてアルバムです。 Next up, the album!
Next up, the album!
This time, it's being released in two formats: the CD and vinyl! Woohoo!
Pre-orders will begin also at 1:15 PM JST at the hololive production official shop, like real soon.
Pre-orders will also begin at 1:15 PM JST at the hololive production official shop, which is very soon.
As for digital releases, that will happen on July 12th.
今回は、CDとレコードの2種類のリリースとなっておりまして、
This time, we have two types of releases: CD and vinyl records.
このあと1時15分より、ホロライブ・オフィシャルショップにて予約が開始されます。
Pre-orders will start on the hololive official shop in a moment at 1:15 PM.
デジタルリリースは、7月12日です。
The digital release is on July 12th.
CDには、ここでしか聴けない「Gravity」のリアレンジ・バージョンと、ステッカー2種。
The CD comes with a rearranged version of "Gravity" that you can only hear here, and two types of stickers.
レコードには、ジャケットとアナザージャケットが印刷されたLPサイズ両面ポスターカードがついてきます。ポストカードじゃないよ。ポスターカード。もっとデカいです。
The record comes with an LP-sized double-sided poster card printed with both the jacket designs. It's not a postcard, it's a poster card. It's much bigger!
さらに、こちらのポスターカードには、両面のどちらかに必ず、直筆サインが入ります！
Furthermore, this poster card will definitely be autographed by hand on one of the sides!
サインされる面は、ランダムでございます。裏面かもしれないし、表面かもしれません。
Which side gets signed is random. It might be the back side, or it might be the front side.
The CD will include an exclusive rearranged version of "Gravity" and two types of stickers.
While the vinyl comes with a double-sided LP-sized poster card.
Yes, a pretty darn big poster card, featuring both the main and alternate album covers.
Plus, yes a big plus, one side of this poster card will definitely feature a handwritten autograph.
The signed side will be random, so it could be on either the alternate jacket side or the main album cover. We'll see when you get it!
And "Be My Flame", which was performed in today's 3D live, will also be digitally released at midnight today! So don't forget to check it out.
そして、ライブでお披露目した「Be My Flame」は24時にデジタルリリースもあるので、忘れずにチェックしてね！
And "Be My Flame", which I performed on stage, will be digitally released at midnight, so don't forget to check it out!
And there's more! That's right, my first solo live concert! Woohoo!
The venue will be in...
Tokyo at SGC Hall Ariake! Woo!
And it'll be held on a Tuesday on October 6th!
I'm super, super, super excited for this,
and I'm so glad I got to finally announce it!
So, I hope you guys will be really excited for it as well! Yay!
あとね、えっとソロライブも決まりました！
And also, a solo live show has been decided!
場所は東京、SGCホール有明でございます。
The venue is SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo!
えっと、開催される日程は10月6日火曜日です！
And the date it will be held is Tuesday, October 6th!
すっごく楽しみにしてるし、
I'm really looking forward to it,
もうとにかく、もうこんなライブがやれる機会自体が、もうホントに、まさかできると思ってなくて、
and anyway, I never thought I would get an opportunity to do a live show like this.
とってもワクワクしてますし、これからも準備がんばります！
I'm super excited, and I'll do my best preparing for it!
Please look forward to further details and information in the future!
Last but not least, there will be a members-only part
starting at 1:30 PM pretty soon,
so please come check it out if you can, and join the family!
最後に、メン限パートが1時半から始まるので、
Lastly, the members-only part starts at 1:30,
よかったらメンバーに入って見に来てね！
so if you'd like, join the membership and come watch!
では、
Well then,
ありがとうございました！
thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
IRyS for now! Until the members' part!